Guide to the University Archives Photograph Collection, Glass Negatives and Lantern Slides, circa 1890-circa 1960 UA 023.031 UA 023.031
Special Collections Research Center
- Charts and Graphs, Series 4
  - Construction of a magnetic field (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 61)
  - Characteristic hysteresis loop (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 62)
  - Magnetic uniformity curve - piped sample (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 63)
  - Photograph of the flaw indicated in the curve (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 64)
  - Apparatus assembled at the Bureau of standards (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 65)
  - Magnetizing solenoid and test coils (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 66)
  - Diagram of electrical connections (tape has worn off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 67)
  - Record with single test coil (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 68)
  - Record with differential test coils - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 69)
  - Magnetic research - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 70)
  - Magnetic research (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 71)
  - Magnetic research - Fig. 13 - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 72)
  - Magnetic research - Fig. 14 - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 73)
  - Magnetic research - Fig 15 (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 74)
  - Magnetic research - Fig. 16 (tape is wearing off) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 75)
  - Aerial view - unidentified - 47 - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 168)
  - Map - land utilization Rabbit and Cat Creek watershed area - Millshoal Township - Macon County, North Carolina - April 1937 - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 169)
  - Map - Soil survey Rabbit and Cat Creek watershed area - Millshoal Township - Macon County, North Carolina - April 1937 - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 170)
  - Map - Land ownership Rabbit and Cat Creek watershed area - Millshoal Township Macon County - North Carolina - April 1937 - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 171)
  - Two men in front of chalk board with prices of horses and a lamb written on it - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 172)
  - Chart - Phosphate and limestone - Analysis by Animal Nutrition Division - 1939 Harvest - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 173)
  - Chart - Effect of rate of limestone on total plant cover and species - June 1940 Counts - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 174)
  - Chart - Effect of rate of phosphate and limestone on total dry yields from 1940 Harvest - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 175)
  - Chart - Effect of rate of phosphate on total plant cover and species - June 1940 Counts - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 176)
  - Sources of phosphate 1940 - black and white - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 177)
  - Chart - from abundance to abundance - the cycle of soil depletion and rebuilding - Hand Colored Slides, maps & charts (Cardbox 13, Envelope 178)
- Forests and Woods, Series 5
  - Forest and neat piles of logs - Hand Colored Slides, Woods & Forests (Cardbox 12, Envelope 150)
  - Benches and tables in the woods - Hand Colored Slides, Woods & Forests (Cardbox 12, Envelope 151)
  - People standing in the woods on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, Woods & Forests (Cardbox 12, Envelope 152)
  - Forest thinning - 4 men in a forest - Hand Colored Slides, Woods & Forest (Cardbox 12, Envelope 153)
  - Trees - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 19)
- 4-H Clubs, Series 6
  - Where Is John? - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 1)
  - I'm On The Upward Trail - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 2)
  - Happy Days - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 3)
  - Home On The Range - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 4)
  - Home On The Range - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 5)
  - Home On The Range - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 6)
  - Let Me Call You Sweetheart - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 7)
  - The More We Meet Together - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 8)
  - In The Evening by The Moonlight - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 9)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 10)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 11)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 12)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 13)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 14)
  - Down In The Valley - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 15)
  - Under The Spreading Chestnut Tree - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 16)
  - Sweet Adeline - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 17)
  - Long Long Trail - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 18)
  - Mollie Maloney - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 19)
  - The Smoke Goes Up The Chimney - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 20)
  - Little Tom Tinker - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 21)
  - A Plowing Song -1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 22)
  - A Plowing Song -1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 23)
  - A Plowing Song -1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 24)
  - Pussy Willow - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 25)
  - The Windmill - 1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 26)
  - The Windmill - 1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 27)
  - The Windmill - 1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 28)
  - Day Is Dying - 1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 29)
  - Day Is Dying - 1 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 8, Envelope 30)
  - Day Is Dying - continued #3 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 31)
  - Speed Away - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 32)
  - 4-H Clubs Field Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 33)
  - The Song Of Health - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 34)
  - The Song Of Health - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 35)
  - The Song Of Health - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 36)
  - Dreaming - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 37)
  - Dreaming - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 38)
  - Dreaming - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 39)
  - 4-H Clubs Friendship Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 40)
  - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 41)
  - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 42)
  - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 43)
  - Swing Low Sweet Chariot - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 44)
  - Sourwood Mountain - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 45)
  - Sourwood Mountain - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 46)
  - Tiritomba - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 47)
  - Tiritomba - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 48)
  - The Bells Of Saint Mary's - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 49)
  - The Bells Of Saint Mary's - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 50)
  - The Bells Of Saint Mary's - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 51)
  - America The Beautiful - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 52)
  - America The Beautiful - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 53)
  - America - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 54)
  - America - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 55)
  - Dixie - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 56)
  - Dixie - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 57)
  - The Battle Hymn Of The Republic - #2 - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 58)
  - In The Garden - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 59)
  - In The Garden - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 60)
  - In The Garden - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 61)
  - Now The Day Is Over - 4-H Clubs Song Slides [cracked/broken slide] (Cardbox 16, Envelope 62)
  - Day Is Dying In The West - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 63)
  - Day Is Dying In The West - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 64)
  - Day Is Dying In The West - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 65)
  - Morning Comes Early - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 66)
  - Morning Comes Early - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 67)
  - 4-H Clubs Firelight Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 68)
  - 4-H Clubs Firelight Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 69)
  - 4-H Clubs Firelight Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 70)
  - Water Boy - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 71)
  - Water Boy - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 72)
  - Water Boy - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 73)
  - A Camp Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 74)
  - A Camp Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 75)
  - A Camp Song - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 76)
  - Follow The Gleam - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 77)
  - Follow The Gleam - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 78)
  - A Song Of Peace - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 79)
  - A Song Of Peace - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 80)
  - Short'nin' Bread - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 81)
  - Short'nin' Bread - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 82)
  - Short'nin' Bread - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 83)
  - Short'nin' Bread - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 84)
  - Short'nin' Bread - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 85)
  - Come Thou Almighty King (slide is not taped) - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 86)
  - Come Thou Almighty King (slide is not taped) - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 9, Envelope 87)
  - Come Holy Comforter - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 10, Envelope 88)
  - To The Great One In Three - 4-H Clubs Song Slides (Cardbox 10, Envelope 89)
  - Come And Sing With Me (Cardbox 10, Envelope 90)
  - Come And Sing With Me (Cardbox 10, Envelope 91)
  - Sing A Song (Cardbox 10, Envelope 92)
  - Home Sweet Home (Cardbox 10, Envelope 93)
  - Home Sweet Home (Cardbox 10, Envelope 94)
  - Home Sweet Home (Cardbox 10, Envelope 95)
  - Holy Holy Holy (Cardbox 10, Envelope 96)
  - Wonderful Words Of Life (Cardbox 10, Envelope 97)
  - Jesus Loves Me (Cardbox 10, Envelope 98)
  - Jesus Loves Me (Cardbox 10, Envelope 99)
  - The Golden Rule (Cardbox 10, Envelope 100)
  - Come All You Club Girls (Cardbox 10, Envelope 101)
  - Come All You Club Girls (Cardbox 10, Envelope 102)
  - The Keeper (Cardbox 10, Envelope 103)
  - The Keeper (Cardbox 10, Envelope 104)
  - The Keeper (Cardbox 10, Envelope 105)
  - The Keeper (Cardbox 10, Envelope 106)
  - Hello (Cardbox 10, Envelope 107)
  - Dr. S. A. Knapp's, "Ten Commandments of Agriculture." - 1910 Corn Club work in Buncombe - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research - Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 1)
  - Dr. S. A. Knapp's, "Ten Commandments of Agriculture." - 1910 Corn Club week in Buncombe, by C. F. Ray - Asheville, North Carolina - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 4)
  - A demonstration in testing seed corn to six club boys - US Dept. Of Agriculture - S. 109 #18, Neg. No. 12383-B - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 5)
  - Buncombe County Corn club - 1915 Corn Club Boys - by C. F. Ray - Asheville, North Carolina - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 6)
  - Buncombe County, North Carolina Corn Club 1915 - preparation of prize acre in 1915 - by C. F. Ray, Asheville, North Carolina - plowing with a horse drawn plow - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 7)
  - Buncombe County Corn Club - 1915 - A boy and a pile of corn cobs - by C. F. Ray, Asheville, North Carolina - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 9)
  - Five children standing next to 3 swine (slide is cracked) - Students in class or working on assignment on campus. Old state fairgrounds are in the background (Cardbox 18, Envelope 21)
- North Carolina State University Campus, Series 7
  - Broughton Hall
    - New Mechanical Engineering Building - Construction - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 18)
    - Diesel building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 20)
    - Diesel Laboratory - large unit - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 45)
  - Bureau of Mines
    - Bureau of Mines building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 11)
    - Bureau of Mines building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 45)
  - Burlington Engineering Laboratories
    - Reactor under construction - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 30)
    - Radioactive gas disposal system, diagram - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 2)
    - Professor at the Nuclear Reactor - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 2A)
    - Operational summary of NCSCR-1, 1954, 1955 - chart - (tape is wearing off slide) - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 3)
    - Operator at the reactor's control board - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 3A)
    - Operational summary of NCSCR-3 - chart - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 4)
    - Parts - S-16 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 4A)
    - Reactor shield, cutaway drawing - film slide, not glass - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 5)
    - Reactor parts and a man - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 6)
    - Nuclear reactor project equipment - gloves and instruments (slide is cracked) - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 7)
    - Nuclear reactor control board - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 8)
    - Nuclear reactor control equipment and two men - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 9)
    - Nuclear reactor control equipment, and six people, similar to slide 18 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 11)
    - Wake county reactor site map - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 12)
    - N C State College map showing location of buildings on campus - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 13)
    - Nuclear engineering graduates, statistical graph, 1951-1960 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 14)
    - Equipment - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 15)
    - Figure 8-B Reactor Control and Instrumentation Block Diagram (tape is wearing off) - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 15A)
    - Equipment, and two people - two pictures - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 16)
    - Reactor part - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 17)
    - Reactor control board, and nine people, similar to slide 11 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 18)
    - Reactor parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 19)
    - Nuclear reactor - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 [slide cracked] (Cardbox 16, Envelope 19A)
    - Reactor parts and two men - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 20)
    - A man at the reactor control board - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 21)
    - Reactor parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 22)
    - Reactor parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 23)
    - Empty classroom - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 24)
    - Reactor control board - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 25)
    - Instrumentation of NCSCR-3, diagram - 7 July 1961 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 26)
    - Reactor parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 27)
    - Operational Summary of NCSCR-2, 1957-1959 and 1960, chart - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 28)
    - Reactor parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 29)
    - North Carolina State College physics Department and Fuel and Gas handling system for NCSCR-4, 3 June 1959 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 30)
    - Burlington Engineering Laboratories - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 31)
    - Parts - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 65)
    - Nuclear reactor - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 77)
    - Burlington Engineering Laboratories - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 78)
    - Bowery at Center Street (diagram) - floor plan - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 88)
    - Equipment Room, Neg. No 5-60-3 - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 96)
  - Ceramic Engineering Building
    - Ceramic Engineering Building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 10)
    - Ceramic Engineering Building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 19)
  - Cox Hall
    - A. C. Menius - Cox Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 1)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 31)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 32)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 4)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 5)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 33)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 34)
    - A. C. Menius - Lab Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office (Cardbox 4, Envelope 35)
  - Daniels Hall
    - Electrical Engineering Department - First solid state lab in Daniels 423 est. by R. Lade 1963 - Buildings and Grounds (Cardbox 4, Envelope 2)
    - Electrical Engineering Department - First solid state lab in Daniels 423 est. by R. Lade 1963 - Buildings and Grounds (Cardbox 4, Envelope 3)
    - Physics Department - radio frequency ion source - man sitting - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 49)
    - Physics Department - decomposition of nickel carbonyl - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 50)
    - Electrical Engineering - dynamo laboratory - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 36)
    - Electrical Engineering - students' lab communications - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 37)
    - Daniels Hall - probably early 1960s - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 76)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering - 1st Solid St. lab (lab?) - Daniels Hall - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 77)
  - Engineering Research Building
    - Engineering research building with State College chimney - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 1)
    - Engineering research building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 2)
    - Shop building with cars in front - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 22)
    - Industrial Engineering - machine shop with people - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 35)
  - Holladay Hall
    - Holladay Hall with cannon in front - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 38)
    - Campus - Holladay Hall, Tompkins, dorms, barn (broken negative) (Cardbox 17, Envelope 1)
  - King Religious Center
    - King, circa 1914, YMCA - Similar views in King Religious Center file in Photograph Collection - Buildings and Grounds - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 23)
  - Leazar Hall
    - Leazar, circa 1914 - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 40)
  - Machinery and Equipment
    - Electrical Engineering machinery? - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 13)
    - Textile machinery - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 14)
    - Textiles machinery and students - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 36)
    - Textiles machinery - NCSU Campus [slide cracked] (Cardbox 16, Envelope 16)
    - Machinery (electrical engineering?) - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 37)
    - Rack dryer for drying lightweight extruded tile - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 4)
    - Electric dryer showing extruded and dress-press lightweight tile - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 5)
    - 50-ton hydraulic dry press for work in refractories - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 6)
    - George - hydraulic block machine - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 7)
    - George - hydraulic block machine - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 8)
    - Spray booth on left, Lancaster mixer in center, heavy duty electric furnace directly in back - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 9)
    - Mechanical Engineering - Westinghouse turbine unit - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 51)
    - Mechanical Engineering - general view of steam lab - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 32)
    - Mechanical Engineering - heating and air conditioning lab - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 33)
    - Ceramic Engineering lab - hydraulic presses for electrical porcelains - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 34)
    - Equipment (back painted) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 2)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 3)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 4)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 5)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 6)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 7)
    - Equipment - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 8)
    - Lab - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 9)
    - Lab equipment (painted on back) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 10)
    - Lab - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 11)
    - Lab - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 12)
  - Memorial Bell Tower
    - Memorial Tower - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 15)
    - Memorial Tower (tape is wearing off of slide) - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 46)
  - 1911 Building
    - Campus view - 1911 Building, Riddick Field, and Shops - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 39)
    - Buildings and Grounds - 1911 Building (slide is cracked) (Cardbox 18, Envelope 2)
    - Buildings and Grounds - 1911 Building (slide is broken) (Cardbox 18, Envelope 3)
  - Page Hall
    - Page Hall - Mechanical Engineering - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 17)
  - Patterson Hall
    - Patterson, circa 1915 - See Photograph Collection - Buildings and Grounds - Patterson for similar photographs - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 25)
  - Pullen Hall
    - Pullen Hall and campus - 1915, no. 84, neg. #105 - See Photograph Collection - Buildings and Grounds - Pullen Hall - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 9)
  - Reynolds Coliseum
    - Coliseum with railroad tracks in front - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 47)
  - Ricks Hall